f95zone.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy policy | F95zone

We are F95zone ("we", "our", "us"). We’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. If you have questions about your personal information please [contact us](https://f95zone.to/pages/contact/).

## Privacy

For your peace of mind, we would like to ensure that **under no circumstances** will your email be shared with (or distributed to) anyone. Your privacy is extremely important, and we’re not kidding. Since the site allows user contributions and posts, it’s strongly recommended you don’t share your email publicly when posting. 

Joining only requires an email address which is the only unique & reliable identifier for our users. We ask for no other identifier. Since you are permitted to change your “display name” anytime, your login is always your original registered email. There are no “name” fields, so you are not required or encouraged to use your real name, nor submit any other personal information, address or phone number. 

We do not know your password. It is stored in an encrypted hash. You may [reset your password anytime](https://f95zone.com/lost-password/) and the previous reset limit has been lifted. We also recently removed the forcing of very strong passwords when resetting. Once you are logged in, the account/settings page permits you to change your password. 

Users may voluntarily enter their city (or country) on their profile card to let other users know where they are located – purely for interests sake and no other reason. It is nice to know when someone is from another country so that we may translate our communications into their native language. We strongly encourage an international community as we are multi-lingual ourselves. 

Naturally, some basic and general information (such as browser type, device, and IP address etc.) is occasionally logged along with any submissions for visitors & statistic purposes, and these are essential for gaining a general knowledge of our audience. It also assists in debugging , depending on what browser/device you’re using. 

+---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------+

##  Forum Registration 

Registration is necessary to be able to participate and post in our forum, a registration form should be filled out completely with your desired username, password and email address. Your email address will be used to verify your membership and to contact you about forum related concerns. F95zone.com retains sole ownership of all the information collected on this website. We do not share any personally identifying information with outside third parties. 

##  Forum User Information 

If you are a forum member, please be aware that when you share or post personally identifying information, that that information can be seen, stored or utilized by other forum members whom you chose to share the information with. This may result in you receiving unsolicited messages and other forms of communication, depending on the information you shared. F95zone.com will not be responsible for personally identifying information that you share or post in the forum. 

##  Log Files 

Log files contain information that is usually made available by your web browser and is stored on our web server. This non personally identifying information includes the following: browser type, language preference, referring site and the date and time of every page request. Just like most other sites, we collect this information to: have a better understanding of how our visitors use our website, be able to generate reports on the trends relevant to the usage of our website, help with website administration, analyze user activities on the site, and collect information about our user base in general. We do not link the information contained in these log files to personally identifying information and we will never distribute them to outside third parties. 

Further data may be collected if you choose to share it, such as if you fill out fields on your profile.

##  What information we collect 

When using forums provided by F95zone.com, we may require some or all of the following information: 

  * email address
  * Internet Protocol (IP) address
  * geographical location
  * browser type and version
  * operating system
  * referral source
  * length of visit, page views, website navigation and any other related browsing activity

##  Cookies and Web Beacons 

A cookie is a small text file that a website stores on your computer. This file contains information that your browser provides to the website each time you return. Cookies are used for record keeping purposes. A web beacon is a transparent graphical image that serves to monitor your interaction with a website. This, along with cookies and log files, provides us with analytical information that we can use to improve website performance and user experience in general. We do not link this information to personally identifying information nor do we give this information to outside third parties. This privacy statement regarding the use of cookies and web beacons is only applicable to the F95zone.com website. 

We have a detailed cookie policy and more information about the cookies that we set on this page. 

##  Third Party Ads 

Our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons in the ads that they serve on our website. The use of such technologies will enable the advertiser to store information about your web surfing interests, so that they can show you targeted advertisements that they believe will interest you the most. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies and web beacons in the ads of our third party advertisers. 

##  Managing Cookies 

If you do not wish to enable cookies, simply adjust your browser settings before using our website and turn off cookies for F95zone.com or our third party advertisers. Bear in mind, however, that disabling cookies may affect how our site will function for you (e.g. being unable to log in). 

##  Links to Other Sites 

Our website contains links leading to other websites that are not owned or managed by us. Because we are not responsible for how these sites handle your privacy, we encourage you to check out the Privacy Policies of those other websites before giving out your personal information. 

## Keeping your data secure

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

##  Controlling your personal information 

When using the F95zone.com forum, you may choose to limit public viewing of applicable personal information through the settings located in the Privacy section of your account. 

F95zone.com will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties. We may use your personal information to send you security information, updates, or other information pertaining to F95zone.com , or your account.

## Rights

You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you or obtain a copy of it. To do so please [contact us](https://f95zone.to/pages/contact/). If you believe that the information we hold for you is incomplete or inaccurate, you may [contact us](https://f95zone.to/pages/contact/) to ask us to complete or correct that information.

You also have the right to request the erasure of your personal data. Please [contact us](https://f95zone.to/pages/contact/) if you would like us to remove your personal data.

## Acceptance of this policy

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

## Changes to this policy

We may make changes to this policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future.

**Last updated:** December 20, 2018
